http://www.net-commerce-solutions.co.uk/privacy.html

About NCS
Why Choose Us?
Hertfordshire Web Design Company NCS Privacy Statement
Hertfordshire web design company NCS agrees to keep the business affairs and information of you, the Client, confidential except where necessary for the execution of our services to you, authorised as part of the publication of your website or by legal requirements.
Email Addresses
We shall use email addresses received on a consensual basis from newsletter subscribers for NCS contact purposes only and not disclose these to and for the use of  third parties. Consent can be withdrawn at any time by email to data@net-commerce-solutions.co.uk or by use of the unsubscribe option in our emails.
Other Personal Information
We record contact information for our existing clients and prospective clients for normal contractual and legitimate interest business purposes including invoicing, service reminders and updates. We do not disclose these to and for the use of third parties.  Past or prospective clients can request deletion of their data and cancellation of further contact at any time.
NCS follow General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) standards for personal data.  Any complaints on the handling of personal data can be sent to data@net-commerce-solutions.co.uk or to the GDPR regulatory body.
Use of Cookies
This site uses small files known as cookies to help provide our service to you through measuring how you and other people use our site, so we can improve it for future visitors.
Cookies cannot be used to identify you personally. You can manage these small files yourself and learn more about them through "Internet browser cookies - what they are and how to manage them." In particular, you can set your browser to stop cookies being used.
We take your continuing to use our website as implied permission for us to use cookies for these purposes if you have set your browser to allow this.
Our Newsletter NetNews Service similarly uses anonymous small cookie like files for monitoring newsletter usage. Signing up for our newsletter and continuing your registration provides implied consent to our use of these. You can deregister at any time by emailing us or clicking on an automatic cancellation link which appears on every newsletter.
Net Commerce Solutions
Hertfordshire Web Design Company Privacy Policy
Testimonials
"We are so delighted with the work you have put in and the fabulous end result"
Paul BallandJ W Flowers
more testimonials
Custom Web Design
From only £499
For 5 Pages
07788 198283 (Harpenden Office)
01438 798 638 (Welwyn Office)
Popular Links
Free Consultation
Web Design Portfolio
Search Engine Marketing
Pay per Click
Property Sites
Online Sales
E-mail Marketing
Hosting & Domains
Our Latest Newsletter
Articles
Newsletter Sign Up
Please enter your email address to receive our regular newsletter:
Sign Up >
Home
Website Design
Search Engines
Web Marketing
Portfolio
Hosting
Contact
Privacy
Site Plan
Cookie Policy - This site uses cookies to help monitor usage
Email Us or call us on 07788 198283 (Harpenden Office) or 01438 798 638 (Welwyn Office)
Offices: 6 Bramble Close, Harpenden, Hertfordshire, AL5 4AN; 1 Burnham Close, Burnham Green, Welwyn, Hertfordshire, AL6 0PERegistered Office: 6 Bramble Close, Harpenden, Hertfordshire, AL5 4AN Registered in England and Wales Company number 4052885, Vat No. 727 5078 20
